No one is lost without a trace.
Searching is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Aneesh Chaganty.
After David Kim's 16-year-old daughter goes missing, a local
investigation is opened and a detective is assigned to the case.
But 37 hours later and without a single lead, David decides to search the one place no one
has looked yet, where all secrets are kept today: his daughter's laptop.
David Kim, played by John Cho.
Margot, played by Michelle La.
Detective Vick, played by Debra Messing.
Peter, played by Joseph Lee.
Pamela Nam Kim, played by Sara Sohn.
Abigail, played by Briana McLean.
Searching is a 2018 American screenlife mystery thriller film directed by Aneesh Chaganty in his
feature debut, written by Chaganty and Sev Ohanian and produced by Timur Bekmambetov.
Set almost entirely on computer screens and smartphones, the film follows a father (John Cho) trying to find his
missing 16-year-old daughter (Michelle La) with the help of a police detective (Debra Messing).
This was the first mainstream Hollywood thriller
headlined by an Asian-American actor.
A co-production between the United States and Russia, the film
premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 21, 2018.
It was released in a limited release on August 24, 2018, before
opening wide on August 31, 2018 by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film was a financial and critical success, grossing over $75 million worldwide against a $880,000 budget and
receiving praise for its direction, acting, unique visual presentation, and unpredictable storyline.
At the Independent Spirit Awards, Cho was nominated for Best Male Lead.
The film's success launched a titular film series including a standalone
installment titled Run, and a follow-up titled Missing.
The film explores themes of california, stalker,
disappearance, internet, east asian lead.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.